제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
위스콘신주 포인트 플레이스
Point Place, Wisconsin
목요일 오후
Thursday Afternoon
오후 4시 17분
4:17 p.m.
에릭네 지하실
Eric Forman's Basement
- 준비됐지?
- 그래
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
너무 느려
Too slow.
오, 인제 어떻게 하는 건지 알았어
각오해
Oh, I see how this game is done.
Now my turn.
- 준비됐지?
- 그래
- Ready?
- Yeah.
너무 느려
Too slow.
페즈, 그렇게 하는 게 아냐
손을 때려야지
No, Fez, that's not how the game works.
You're supposed to hit my hands.
너무 느려
Too slow.
- 쿠키 먹을 사람?
- 저요
- Who wants cookies?
- Cool.
너무 감사합니다
- Thank you very much.
- They're carob. Nature's chocolate.
캐롭이라고, 자연의 초콜릿이란다
지중해 연안의 구주 콩나무
- 전 됐어요
- 저도요
- I think not.
- No.
왜들 이러니
Come on.
내가 말 안해 줬으면
모르고들 먹었을 거 아냐
You wouldn't have known
if I hadn't told you.
에릭, 내가 너 직업체험 때 입을
정말 멋진 옷 골라 놨단다
Eric, I picked out a really snazzy
outfit for you to wear on Career Day.
아유, 신나라
That's goody.
뚱하기는..
Fine, Mr. Grumpy...
그래도 얼른 직장 동료들에게
내 아들 자랑하고 싶어 죽겠구나
but I can't wait to show off
my little man at work.
있죠? 저도 그래요
You know what?
Me neither.
도와줘
Help me.
웬 직업체험?
정말 짜증난다
Why Career Day, man?
It's so lame.
그거야 너희 엄마가
급식 아줌마니까 그렇지
That's just 'cause
your mom's the lunch lady.
너희 엄마가 '욕쟁이 에드나'니?
Your mom is Gross Edna?
내 말은, 멋지시다고
I mean, cool.
맞아, 멋지실 거야
You bet it's cool.
그래서 난 하이드 엄마하고
직업체험을 하기로 했거든, 맞지?
That's why I'm spending the day
with Hyde and his mom. Right?
에릭, 차고로 좀 와 봐라
Eric, I need you in the garage.
네. 금방 갔다 올께
Okay. Look, I'll be right back.
네가 네 차에다 뭔 짓을
했는지 확실히 알려주마
You can explain exactly
what you did to this car.
얘들아, 내일 보자
Okay. Look, I'll see you tomorrow.
라이트 좀 잘 잡아라
Hold the light steady.
더 위로
Higher.
내 눈에는 왜 비춰!
Not in my eyes!
내가 카뷰레터로 보이냐?
Do I look like a carburetor?
어두워서 잘 모르겠어요
Not in this light.
첫번째 경고다
That's one.
죄송해요
Sorry.
에릭, 너도 이제 고등학생이다
Eric, you're in high school.
학교에서 뜨개질 가르치는
시간을 5분만 쪼개면
You'd think they'd take
5 minutes out of teaching macrame...
플래쉬 비추는 법 정도는
가르칠 수 있을 거야
and show you how to hold
a damned flashlight!
그거 대학에서 가르치는 거
아니었나요?
Dad, isn't that what college is for?
두번째 경고다
세번째까지 가보고 싶냐?
That's two.
You wanna go for three?
이리 줘
Give me that.
이 빌어먹을 것이 나갔구나
See, the damn thing is shot.
복구 킷트가 필요해
I need a rebuild kit.
이건 내일 하자
We'll work on this tomorrow.
- 아빠, 내일은 직업체험 날이에요
- 난 하프타임만 일하니까
- Dad, tomorrow's Career Day.
- Yeah, I'm working half-days.
정오에는 집에 올 거다
I'll be home by noon.
직업체험은 엄마하고
병원에서 하려고 했는데요
I think I'm gonna go
to the hospital with mom.
그래, 왜?
Yeah, what for?
직업체험이니까요
하프타임 체험이 아니고
It's Career Day, not Career Half-Day.
아뇨, 이건 경고감이 아니에요
선생님이 시키신 거라구요
Okay, look, that's not three,
that's what my teacher said....
알았다, 난 차를 고칠테니
Fine, Eric. I'll fix the car...
넌 엄마랑 가서 장차 간호사가
되고 싶은지 알아 봐라
and you go with your mom
and see if you want to be a nurse.
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정, 번역 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
1x18 The Career Day
Feb 28, 1999 on FOX
여기가 내가 근무하는 병동이야
Okay, so, now, this is my ward.
난 야간 간호사랑 돌아보고 올테니
아가씨들하고 인사 나누렴
I have to check with the night nurse.
You say hi to the girls.
안녕, 아가씨들
Hi, girls.
안녕, 네가 에릭이구나
사진을 많이 봐서 금방 알겠다
Hi. You must be Eric.
I recognize you from all the pictures.
너 얼굴이 정말 깨끗해 졌구나
Your face has cleared up real nice.
알아봐 주셔서 고마워요
Thanks for noticing that.
너희 엄마는 간호사
다섯사람 몫을 하고 계셔
You know, your mom does the work
of five nurses.
여긴 정말
너희 엄마없이는 안된단다
This place would fall
apart without her.
- 게다가 아주 웃기시지!
- 네, 맞아요
- And she's so funny!
- Yeah, she is.
잠깐, 아니에요, 웃기다뇨
Wait, no, she's not.
아니긴, 너희 엄마가
정말 웃긴 만화를 그렸는데, 볼래?
Oh, yeah. And she draws
these funny cartoons. See?
미리 말해두는데
이거 약간 야해, 그치만..
Now, I warn you,
it's a little racy, but--
얘야, 넌 볼 필요 없단다
Oh, honey,
you don't need to see that.
이건 그냥 특정 인체 일부인데
It's just, a certain body part...
재밌어 보이라고 다른 인체 일부가
들어차 있는 걸 그린 거야
has been shoved up
another body part for comic effect.
So have you met everybody?
다들 인사는 나눴니?
포먼 간호사
방금 실험실에 물어봤는데
Nurse Forman,
I just talked to the lab.
왜 혈액 샘플을 안 내려 보냈죠?
Why didn't you bring down
that blood sample?
안 주셨으니까요?
Because you didn't give it to me?
안 줬을 리가 있나요
I most certainly did.
다음에 내가 뭘 줘야 될 게 있으면
나한테 말해 줘요
Next time I have something
to give you, you tell me.
그러죠
Will do.
대체 왜 저런데요?
What is his problem?
글쎄, 내 생각은 전에도 말했잖아
Well, you all know my theory.
- 엄마
- 스티븐
- Edna.
- Steven.
페즈, 우리 엄마야
Fez, this is, my mom.
만나서 반가워요
욕쟁이 에드나 부인
Nice to meet you,
Mrs. Gross Edna.
아냐, 욕쟁이 '에드나 양'이라고 불러
No, honey. It's Miss Gross Edna.
욕쟁이 '에드나 씨'는
빵빵한 엉덩이양하고 도망갔어
You see, Mr. Gross Edna ran off
with Miss Perfect Ass.
지금은 웃으면서 말할 수 있지
But she can laugh about it now.
물론이지. 닥쳐
Yes, she can. Shut up.
식품 서비스 산업을 체험하게 돼서
너무 흥분돼요
I am so excited to be in
the food service industry.
제가 치즈를 잘라도 될까요?
May I cut the cheese?
얘 농담하는 거니?
Is he kidding?
어찌 알겠어요
We can never tell.
맘대로 하렴
Knock yourself out.
대신 손가락을 자르면
여기서 그랬다고 하지마
But if you cut off a finger,
you're out of here.
스티븐, 넌 피자 자르는 거 부터 해
Steven, you can start
by slicing pizza.
아뇨, 아뇨
전 관찰하러 온 거예요
No. I'm here as an observer.
벽에 붙은 파리처럼요
관찰자가 꽤 많네요
A fly on the wall. One of many.
놀랍기도 해라
꼭 지 애비처럼 게으르기는
What a surprise.
Lazy, just like your father.
아뇨, 완전히 나만의 방식으로
게으른 거에요
No, actually, I'm lazy in a way
that's entirely my own.
두사람 정말 재밌게 노네요
You two are hilarious.
- 자, 이거 써라
- 난 안 쓸거예요
- Here, put these on.
- I'm not wearing these.
미안한데, 나도 좋아서 이러는게 아냐
이건 그 바보같은..
Crap, sorry, don't blame me.
It's the stupid....
그놈의 보건규정 탓이야
Those health codes.
저 이거 가져도 돼요?
May I keep these?
물론이지, 아가
Sure, baby.
너무 멋져요
우리 아빠 사무실이네요
This is so cool.
My dad's office.
아빠 책상
Dad's desk.
아빠 전화, 따르릉-따르릉
Dad's phone, ding-ding.
우리 아빠
My dad.
여기 정말 맘에 들어요
Yeah, I love this.
그래, 마이클, 이곳은 대단한 일이
이루어 지는 곳이란다
Yeah, Michael, this is where
all the magic happens.
좋아요, 시작하죠
Okay, let's get started.
질문 1: "당신의 직업은 뭡니까?"
Question number one:
"What's your job?"
나는 통계 분석 기술 이사란다
I'm a senior executive,
statistical analysis technician.
- 무슨 이사라구요?
- 쉽게 말하자면..
- You're a senior execu-what?
- In plain English...
난 데이타의 잠재된 활용도를 극대화하기
위해 다양한 통계정보를 규합한단다
I concatenate diverse
statistical information...
to maximize the potential
utilization of data.
그러니까..
So...
사람들에게 데이타를 주시는 거네요?
you give people data?
많이들 그렇게 생각하는데
아니다
You know, a lot of people think that.
No.
내 일은 정보를 출력하는 게 아니라
처리하는 거지
My job's not about output,
it's about throughput.
그러니까 자료를 처리하시는 거네요?
So you throughput data?
이해를 못하고 있구나
Now you've lost me, son.
들어 보렴
Listen, Michael...
네가 좋아하는 8트랙 테잎들 알지?
you know the eight-tracks
you love so much?
- 그거 만드세요?
- 아니
- You make them?
- No.
그렇지만 우리 덕분에 그걸 만드는
사람들이 더 잘 만들 수 있는 거란다
But because of us,
other people who make them...
are able to make them better.
뭘 고치시는군요?
So you fix stuff?
그렇게 볼 수도 있겠지
You could say that.
하지만 아니란다
But I wouldn't.
날짜를 아주 잘 잡았구나, 도나
You picked a good day
to do this, Donna.
3일간의 판촉 세일 첫날이거든
We're starting
a three-day promotional sale.
다들 왜 나를 바겐 밥이라고
부르는지 알게 될거야
You'll finally get to see
why they call me Bargain Bob.
네, 아빠
그게 정말 궁금했어요
Yeah, Dad, 'cause that's been
a real stumper.
귀여운 것 같으니
You're such a cutie.
눈 크게 뜨고 잘 봐
그리고 잘 적도록 해
You keep your eyes peeled
and your pencil sharp...
진정한 사업가의 수완을
배우게 될테니까
because you're gonna learn
how a serious businessman operates.
좋았어, 광대들이 오는구나
Good, the clowns are here.
안녕하세요, 아저씨
집에서 뭐하세요?
Hello, Mr. Forman,
what are you doing home?
아, 맞다
파트타임으로 일 하시죠
That's right,
you're only working part-time.
위로가 될지 모르겠는데
아빠가 아저씨를 정말 불쌍해 하세요
If it makes you feel any better,
my dad feels really, really sorry for you.
너 직업체험 갔어야 되는 거 아니냐?
Aren't you supposed
to be at Career Day?
아뇨, 전 2학년이에요
No, I'm a sophomore.
저에 대해 그런 것도
모르시다니 너무 하세요
I'm surprised
you didn't know that about me.
맞다. 미안하다
Right. My mistake.
여기 있는 동안 저기 카뷰레타에
플래쉬 좀 비춰주지 않을래?
Listen, while you're here,
why don't you hold this flashlight...
on that carburetor there.
이렇게요?
Like this?
이럴 수가!
My God. One of you is not useless.
쓸모있는 녀석이 하나는 있었군
직업의 세계가 당신을
기다리고 있습니다
A world of careers
is waiting for you.
오늘 진로 상담교사와 상의하세요
Talk to your guidance
counselor today.
이 사람들은 미래의 직업을
위한 준비가 돼있습니다
These people are ready
for the jobs of tomorrow.
당신도 그렇습니까?
Are you?
안녕하세요! 이쪽은 내 아들인데
나랑 같이 회진을 돌고 있답니다
Good morning! This is my son.
He's making my rounds with me.
너무 심하다 싶으면
바로 말하렴
You let me know
if this gets to be too much for you.
알았어요, 이 정도는 감당할 수..
어머나! 저게 뭐예요?
Okay, Mom, I think that I can handle it....
Good God! What is that?
나중에 스케이트 보드 타고 싶거든
이걸 떠올려 보렴
Remember this the next time
you want a skateboard.
나쁜 소식입니다
I have some bad news.
오! 좋은 소식입니다
Oh. I have some good news.
좋아요, 힘줘요!
Okay, now push!
- 부인, 손 아파요
- 네가 아픈 게 뭔지나 알아?!
- Ma'am, you're hurting me.
- You don't know what pain is!
알았어요
Okay.
좋다
All right.
이게 우리한테 일을 맡기기 전
매출 동향 지수란다
This is the performance index
before my involvement.
그리고 이건..
And this...
맡긴 다음이지
is after.
그러니까, 요만큼 증진시킨 거네요
Okay. So, you're
responsible for this.
그런 거로 날 평가하면 안 된단다
그 정도면 통계적으로 의미가 없거든
You can't credit me with that.
That's probably a statistical anomaly.
그래도 차트는 아빠가 만드신 거죠?
But you made the chart, right?
그럼 얼마나 좋겠니!
I wish.
저도요
So do I.
좋아요, 질문 3:
Okay, question number three:
"음식 서비스 산업이
당신의 1지망 직업이었나요?"
"Was the food service industry
your first career choice?"
그럴 리가
Heck, no, Fez.
난 항상 쇼 비즈니스에
뛰어들고 싶었단다
I always wanted to go into show biz.
사실, 난 위스콘신 델스의
토미 바틀렛 수상 쇼에서 일했었단다
델튼 호변의 휴양지
In fact, I was in
the Tommy Bartlett water show...
at the Wisconsin Dells.
여자들이 비키니입고 수상스키 타죠
Yes, women waterskiing in bikinis.
정말 에로틱해요
Very erotic.
어쨌든..
Anyway...
난 그 쇼 인간 피라미드
꼭대기에 있었다고
I was the top girl on the pyramid...
임신하는 바람에 짤리기 전엔 말야
when they fired me
for getting knocked up.
그 다음은 내가 할께요, 엄마
Let me finish this one for you, Edna.
그러니까 나 때문에 엄마가 대단하신
수상스키쇼 일을 관두셨다는 얘기야
Fez, this is the story where I ruin
my mother's fabulous water skiing career.
그래, 맞아
Yeah, you did.
임신한 여자가 수상스키 타면
관객들이 거북해할 거랬어
They said a pregnant girl on water skis
would make the audience nervous.
아줌마가 꼴불견으로 뚱뚱해진건
말할 것도 없었겠죠
Not to mention, you were
probably hideously fat.
아냐, 몸매 괜찮았어
담배로 체중관리 했었단 말야
No. I looked great.
I kept my weight down by smoking.
봤지, 엄청난 모성본능 아니냐?
See, that's that maternal instinct
kicking in again.
내 모성애가 어디가 어때서?
Yeah, you're damn right I'm maternal.
- 난 혼자서 널 키웠어
- 혼자요? 그럴리가요
- I raised you alone.
- Alone? Hardly.
'쳇 삼촌'에, '래리 삼촌'도 있었고
There was "uncle" Chet,
and "uncle" Larry...
맞다. '섹시 뚱보 쟈니 삼촌'도 있었죠
and yeah, "uncle" hot tub Johnny.
네 아빠가 도망갔을 때
내가 수녀라도 됐어야 했나 보구나
I suppose I should've just become a nun
when your father walked out on me.
아빠가 얼마나 미칠 것 같으면
도망을 갔겠어요?
Hell, he must've been crazy
to leave all this.
지 애비처럼 입만 살아가지고
Always a smart ass, Steven.
Just like your father.
아빠가 그거 하난 아주 잘했죠
도망가 버린 거요
You know what?
One thing he did do right: He left!
맞아, 맞으니까
너도 딴 놈들처럼 가 버려
All right. That's right, Steven,
just walk. Just like everyone else.
좋아요, 질문 4:
Okay, question number four:
"본인이 사교적인 사람이라고
생각하시나요?"
"Would you say
you are a people person?"
힘내, 재키! 좀 더!
힘내, 젖 먹던 힘까지
Come on, Jackie! Harder!
Come on, give it all you got.
- 됐다!
- 엄마, 해냈어요!
- Yeah!
- My God, I did it!
해냈어요! 제가 타이어를 갈았어요!
I did it! I'm changing a tire!
'낸시 드류'가 된 거 같아요
소설 낸시 드류 시리즈의 주인공 여탐정
I feel like Nancy Drew.
여자도 비상시 대처법 정도는
알고 있어야 한단다
A girl needs to know
what to do in an emergency.
네 아빠가 이런 것도
아직 안 가르쳤다니 의외구나
You know, I'm surprised your father
hasn't taught you this already.
네..
Yeah...
아빤 너무 열심히 일하셔서
저랑 같이 같이 보내실 시간이 없어요
Daddy works really hard, so he
doesn't spend a lot of time with me.
그치만 제 생일에 '무스탕' 차를
사 준다고 하셨어요
But he did promise me
a Mustang for my birthday.
그래서 전 아빨 사랑해요
So I love him.
있잖냐, 재키
나도 아빠가 된지 오래 됐단다
You know, Jackie,
I've been a father a long time...
그러니까 내 말을 믿어라
so trust me when I tell you this.
'무스탕'은 앞부분에 문제가 있단다
그러니 '파이어 버드'를 사렴
The Mustang's front end is
problematic. Get yourself a Firebird.
해리스 씨한테 페니실린을
주사와 경구, 풀코스로 투입하세요
All right, let's start Mr. Harris
on a full course of penicillin.
선생님, 에리스로마이신을
고려해 보셔야 할 것 같은데요
Doctor, you might
want to consider erythromycin.
내가 왜 간호사 말을 들어야 되죠?
And why would
I want to do that, nurse?
그게요, 해리스 씨가
페니실린 과민반응이 있거든요
It's just that,
Mr. Harris is allergic to penicillin...
에리스로마이신이 그나마
그 사람을 안 죽일 것 같아서요
and I thought erythromycin
might make him a touch less dead.
제 생각에도 죽고 싶어서 병원에
오지는 않을 것 같아요
I know that when I go to the hospital,
I like to not die.
좋아요..
Okay...
아빠도 소비자가 있으시죠?
do you have customers?
아니, 의뢰인에 가깝단다
No, they're more like clients.
- 하여간 의뢰인은 있으시죠?
- 그런 셈이지
- But you have clients?
- Sort of.
그들에게 뭔가 생산품을 제공하시고요?
And you provide them a product?
서비스에 가깝단다
It's more like a service.
- 서비스요?
- 그게 아니..
- A service?
- Not--
데이타의 잠재된 활용도를
극대화하는 거요?
To maximize the potential utilization
of the data?
그렇게 했다간
우린 망할 거다
If we did that,
we'd go out of business.
아저씨. 에릭 있어요?
Red. Forman around?
아니, 지 엄마랑 직업체험 갔다
No, he's with his mom for Career Day.
그런데 너는 직업체험 안 가고
뭐하는 거냐?
Which is where you're supposed to be.
What's the deal?
Man.
엄마가 저 보고 아빠같다며
괴롭히시잖아요
Edna's riding me again
about being just like my dad.
그래서 나와 버렸어요
So I just took off.
너희 아빠도.. 나가 버리지 않았냐?
Didn't your dad...take off?
심오한 아이러니죠
Irony. Far out.
너희 모자는 아픈 과거가 있잖아
Look, you and your mom
have a bad history.
게다가 두사람 다
And neither of you...
서로의 자존심을 살려주지 못해
can nurture the other's self esteem...
왜냐면 둘 다 과거의 비난과
수치심으로 상처받았으니까
because you've both been damaged
by past criticism and shame.
괜찮으세요?
Are you okay?
내가 파트 타임 일을 하면서
'도나휴 쇼'를 너무 많이 봤나 보다
I'm working half-days,
so I watch a lot of Donahue.
확실치는 않지만
유-조인트를 찾은 거 같아요
Okay, I'm not sure, but I think
I found the u-joint.
정말 잘했다, 재키
God bless you, Jackie.
전 다시 들어가 볼께요
Okay, I'm going back in.
누구 앤더슨 씨를 이동침대로
옮기는 거 좀 도와줄래요?
Could someone help me get
Mr. Anderson on the gurney, please?
- 제가 도와드릴께요, 엄마
- 그러렴
- I'll give you a hand, Mom.
- Okay.
근데, 어디가 아프신 거예요?
So, what's wrong with him?
- 죽었단다
- 어머..
- He's dead.
- Oh, my....
네?
What?
30분 전에 봤던 분 아니에요?
Didn't we just see this guy
a half an hour ago?
얘야, 그때도 죽어 있었단다
너한테 말할 엄두가 안 나더구나
Honey, he was dead then.
I didn't have the heart to tell you.
네가 이 사람을 만나 볼 기회가
없었던 게 아쉽구나
I'm so sorry you didn't get a chance
to meet him.
잠깐만요, 앤더슨씨요?
Wait, Mr. Anderson?
엄마가 저녁식사 때마다
말씀하시던 사람 아니에요?
Isn't this the guy
you always talked about at dinner?
딸이 얼마전에 결혼했다던?
The guy whose daughter
just got married?
그래, 나한테 사진을 보여줬는데
Yeah, he just showed
me the pictures.
정말 아름다운 결혼식이었더구나
It was a beautiful wedding.
이 사람이 그리울 거야
I'm gonna miss him.
그럼, 그쪽 끝을 잡으렴
옮기자꾸나
So, okay, you grab that end,
and let's get moving.
우린 20분 안에 환자들
저녁식사 줘야 된단다
We have to serve dinner
in 20 minutes.
그 다음 여기 '카이 스퀘어' 값을 보고
And then we look
at the chi square here...
여기에다 '표준 편차'를 적용하고
apply the standard deviation here...
이 실용 중앙값으로 결과들의
상관관계를 입증하는 거란다
and correlate the results
with the actualization median here.
이게 내가 하는 일이란다
And that's what I do.
이보다 더 확실하게
말할 수는 없을 거 같구나
And I can't make it
any clearer than that.
나 그냥 아빠가 농부라고 할래요
I'm just gonna say you're a farmer.
좋아요, 다음 질문:
Okay, next question:
"이 일에서 무엇을 배우셨나요?"
"What has this job taught you?"
내가 배운 건
One thing I've learned:
Midgets make money.
난쟁이들이 돈벌이가 된다는 거란다
이유는 나도 몰라, 하여간 사람들이
난쟁이를 보면 믹서기를 사거든
I don't know why, but people see
a midget, they wanna buy a blender.
난쟁이를 보면
인생은 짧다는 생각이 드나봐
I guess it reminds them that life is short.
적어, 적어
Write.
마케팅이 중요하다
소비자에 대해 알아야 한다
Marketing is important.
Know your customer.
내 말이랑 다르잖니
That's not what I said.
내 말은 하나도 안 적었구나
None of this is what I said.
그래요, 아빠. 제가 말을
약간 세련되게 고쳤어요
Sure it is, Dad. I mean, I just
cleaned up the language a bit...
아빠의 위엄을 살리려고요
to make you sound more dignified.
위엄을 살려?
Dignified?
무슨 소리 하는 거냐?
너 내가 창피하다는 거냐?
What are you saying?
You're embarrassed by me?
내가 하는 일이 창피해?
What have I ever done
that's embarrassing?
한번 둘러 보세요
Just look around.
좋다. 내 눈엔 어떻게
보이는지 말해주마
All right. Let me tell you what I see.
네 눈엔 광대로 보여도
내 눈에 네 하버드 등록금으로 보인다
You see clowns, I see your tuition
at Harvard.
네 눈엔 아빠가 서커스 감독으로 보여도
내 눈엔 네가 대학원생으로 보인다
You see your dad as a ringmaster,
I see you going to grad school.
네 눈엔 발레 치마 입은
침팬지로 보여도
You see a chimpanzee in a tutu.
Okay, that just makes me laugh.
그래, 저건 나도 웃긴다
침팬지는 귀여워요
The chimp is cute.
중요한 건, 도나
넌 큰 일을 할 수 있다는 거야
The point is, Donna,
you're capable of great things.
네가 그렇게 되기 위해서
내가 이걸 해야만 한다면
And if this is what I have to do
so you can achieve them...
난 기꺼이 할 거란다
then that's what I'll do.
아빠
Dad.
전 너무 속상해요
I feel really bad.
바겐 밥 가게에서는
아무도 속상하지 않아
Nobody feels
really bad around Bargain Bob!
원숭이한테 물리기 전에는 말이다
Unless you got bit by a monkey.
"Bad Blood" by Neil Sedaka
♪ 나쁜, 나쁜
피, 피 ♪
♪ Bad, bad,
blood, blood ♪
♪ 그것이 당신을 속이고 있네 ♪
♪ is taking you for a ride ♪
♪ 나쁜 피를 해치울 방법은 ♪
♪ the only good thing ♪
♪ about bad blood ♪
♪ 내버려 두는 것뿐 ♪
♪ is letting it slide ♪
엄마, 이떻게 이런 일을 매일 하세요?
Mom, how do you do this every day?
엄마는 계속 보살피는데도
사람들은 아프거나 죽어가잖아요
You're running around
and people are sick and dying--
가엾은 앤더슨씨
I mean, poor Mr. Anderson.
엄마는 그 사람을 아셨잖아요
이런 걸 다 어떻게 감당하세요?
Look, you knew this guy, Mom.
How do you deal with all this?
♪ 이제 우리 차례다 ♪
♪ Here we go now. ♪
♪ - 나쁜
- 나쁜 ♪
♪ - Bad
- Bad ♪
♪ - 피
- 피 ♪
♪ - Blood
- Blood ♪
♪ 그년은 미소지으며 ♪
♪ The bitch is in her smile ♪
♪ 입만 열면 거짓말 하네 ♪
♪ The lie is on her lips ♪
♪ 사악한 것 ♪
♪ Such an evil child ♪
잠깐, 너 뭐하는 거니?
What are you doing?
이 매슥거리는
남은 고기를 버리려고요
Throwing out the disgusting
used meat.
아니야, 얘
여기 이 칠리 양동이에 부어야지
No, sweetie, you've gotta
toss that in the chili bucket.
칠리 양동이요?
The chili bucket?
- 전 그거 쓰레기통인줄 알았어요
- 이런
- I thought that was the garbage.
- No.
- 여기다 뭐 많이 버렸니?
- 꽤 버렸죠
- Have you thrown a lot in there?
- Some.
대부분 다 으스러져서
모를 거니까 괜찮아
Most things just break down
in there. It'll be fine.
- 저 왔어요
- 스티븐, 돌아왔구나
- Hi.
- Steven, you came back.
넌 그게 나한테 어떤 의미인지
모를 거다
You don't know
what that means to me.
- 그래요?
- 그래
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
얘야, 저기 피자 판 좀 닦아 줄래?
Honey, could you clean up
those pizza trays?
나 땡땡이 칠 거거든
I'm gonna skip out early.
내가 칠리 양동이에다 뭐했는지
맞춰볼래? 해보라니까, 맞춰봐
Guess what I did in the chili bucket?
Go ahead, guess.
스티븐, 미안해
Steven, I'm sorry.
내가 그렇게 좋은 엄마는 아니지?
I'm not being a very good mom, am I?
맞아요
No.
좋아, 나한테 더 좋은 생각이 있어
같이 뭔가를 해 보자
All right, I've got a better idea.
Let's do something together.
이리 와, 내가 맥주 사줄게
Come on, I'll buy you a beer.
맥주요?
A beer?
- 그래요, 꽤 좋은 생각이네요
- 가짜 민증 갖고 있지?
- Yeah, that actually sounds good.
- You got your fake ID?
- 아시잖아요
- 내 아들답다
- You know it.
- That's my boy.
"가을은 농부에게
수확의 시기입니다"
"Autumn is harvest time for the farmer.
"동틀녁에 아빠와 나는
들녘으로 나가서"
"At dawn, my dad and I
were out in the field...
"나무에서 싱싱한 당근을 땄습니다"
"picking carrots fresh off the trees."
켈소, 당근은 나무에서..
Kelso, carrots don't....
아냐, 잘했어
그렇게 나둬라
That's good.
You should put that down.
너희들은 졸업하면
뭘 하고 싶니?
So, what do you guys want to do
when you graduate?
Not touch dead people, ever.
죽은 사람은 절대 안 만질 거야
난 내 고국으로 돌아 가고 싶어
I want to go back to my homeland...
위스콘신에서 배운
모든 지식을 가지고 말야
with all that knowledge
I have learned in Wisconsin...
가서 철권통치를 할테다
and rule with an iron fist.
안녕하세요, 아빠
안녕.. 재키
Hey, Dad. Hey, Jackie.
- 에릭, 직업체업은 어땠냐?
- 좋았어요. 많은 걸 배웠어요
- Hi, Eric. How was Career Day?
- It was good. I learned a lot.
잘 됐구나
너도 이제 다른 걸 좀 배워봐라
Good. Now you're going to learn
something else.
재키가 너한테
플래쉬 비추는 법을 알려줄 거다
Jackie's gonna teach you
how to hold a flashlight.
재키가요?
Jackie?
그래, 마침내 네 친구 중에
내 맘에 드는 녀석을 찾았구나
Yeah, I finally found
one of your friends I like.
재키는 사실 제 친구가 아니에요
Jackie isn't really one of my friends.
첫번째 경고야
That's one.
잘 했다
That's how you do that.
번역수정: 김찬미(husseyttl@nate)
최종수정: 김현정(fuchs@nate)
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24